Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Educational News: Manual for Trade Union Educators, 1962; Publication (Box 690, Folder 11)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: BFTU/ICFTU Panafrican Conference on Democracy, Development, and the Defence of Human and Trade Union Rights, 1991; Publication (Box 690, Folder 12)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Migration and Globalisation: The new slaves, 1998; Publication (Box 690, Folder 13)
    Author: Andre Linard
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Nuclear Safety, 1989; Publication (Box 690, Folder 14)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Study Guide: Problems of International Migration, Publication (Box 690, Folder 15)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Reports and Proceedings, 1949-1955 (Box 690, Folder 16)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 691, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Reports and Proceedings, 1955-1969 (Box 691, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Report of the First General Council Meeting, 1952; Publication (Box 691, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 691, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Sixteenth World Congress, 1996; Publication (Box 691, Folder 2)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 691, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The ILWU Story: Six Decades of Militant Unionism, 1997; Publication (Box 691, Folder 3)
    Author: International Longshoremen's Association
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 691, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report on Activities of the Confederation, 1957-1978 (Box 691, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 691, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Asian Seminar on Worker's Education, 1958; Publication (Box 691, Folder 5)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 691, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: International Non-Manual Worker's Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 691, Folder 6)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 692, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Reports and Proceedings, 1969-1992 (Box 692, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the First General Council, 1952; Publication (Box 693, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Reports and Proceedings/Activities, 1957-1996 (Box 693, Folder 3)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Asian Seminar on Worker's Education, 1958; Publication (Box 693, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International Non-Manual Workers, 1961; Publication (Box 693, Folder 5)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Some Aspects of Worker's Participation, 1972; Publication (Box 693, Folder 6)
    Author: Christer Asplund
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Trade Union Guide to Globalisation, 2001; Publication (Box 693, Folder 7)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Handbook, 1963; Publication (Box 693, Folder 9)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Trade Union World, 1943-1945 (Box 693, Folder 10)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report on Hungary, 1957; Publication (Box 693, Folder 11)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 693, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Trade Union Guide to Globalisation, 2004; Publication (Box 693, Folder 12)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 694, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions: What they are, what they do, their structure, 1955; Publication (Box 694, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 694, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Third World Conference Women Worker's Problems, 1968; Publication (Box 694, Folder 2)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 694, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Workers and Trade Unions in the Web of Tourism, 1999; Publication (Box 694, Folder 3)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 694, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Worker's Participation in Industry, Publication (Box 694, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 694, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: You and Your Union, Publication (Box 694, Folder 5)
    Notes: no. 1- 7.9, some 2 copies
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada. International Executive Board, Publication (Box 694, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the International Executive Board, 1937-1939 (Box 694, Folder 6)
    Author: International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada. International Executive Board
    Notes: 13th and 20th biennial
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 694, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Answer of the International Longshoremen's Association to the Report of the New York State Crime Commission Dealing With the Waterfront of the Port of New York, 1953; Publication (Box 694, Folder 7)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 694, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: I.L.A. Newsletter/News Report, 1983-2006 (Box 694, Folder 8)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 694, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The President's Report, 1991; Publication (Box 694, Folder 9)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 694, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of Secretary Treasurer, 1991; Publication (Box 694, Folder 10)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 694, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Special Convention, 1976; Publication (Box 694, Folder 11)
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 694, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Fraternal Outlook, 1941; Publication (Box 694, Folder 12)
    Author: International Workers Order
- International Workers Order, Publication (Box 694, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Our People, the Jew in America, 1944; Publication (Box 694, Folder 13)
- Insurance Agent's International Union, Publication (Box 694, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Biennial Convention, 1953-1955 (Box 694, Folder 14)
    Author: Insurance Agent's International Union
- Insurance Workers of America, Publication (Box 695, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Biennial Convention, 1957; Publication (Box 695, Folder 1)
    Author: Insurance Workers of America
- Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union, Publication (Box 695, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: We Dare Be Free, 1983; Publication (Box 695, Folder 2)
    Author: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 695, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Analysis of negotiation agreement provis, 1969; Publication (Box 695, Folder 3)
    Author: New York State Teachers Association
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 695, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1951-1071 (Box 695, Folder 4)
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 695, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York State Education, 1949-1956 (Box 695, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), Publication (Box 696, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Directory of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), 1973-1984 (Box 696, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 696, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Wage Movement in Canada, 1949-1953 (Box 696, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 696, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1959-1961 (Box 696, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 696, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Rulings as to the Meaning and Application of the Award, 1914; Publication (Box 696, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 696, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Award: Arbitration between the Eastern Railroads and Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1913; Publication (Box 696, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 696, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Negotiating Manual, 1953-1962 (Box 696, Folder 6)
- 1199, National Health and Human Service Employees Union, Publication (Box 697, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1999 SEIU News, 1989-2005 (Box 697, Folder 1)
    Author: 1199, National Health and Human Service Employees Union
    Notes: Selective Years
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 698, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York State Education, 1938-1958 (Box 698, Folder 1)
- Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, Publication (Box 699, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Excerpts from Transcript of Proceedings, 1954; Publication (Box 699, Folder 1)
    Author: Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen
    Notes: Dec.
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 698, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Research Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 698, Folder 2)
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 698, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Handbook on Personnel Practices for Teachers, 1970; Publication (Box 698, Folder 3)
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 698, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Non-Professional School Employee Contracts, 1971; Publication (Box 698, Folder 4)
- New York State Teachers Association, Publication (Box 698, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Recent Negotiation Settlements, 1972; Publication (Box 698, Folder 5)
- Insurance Workers of America, Publication (Box 698, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Insurance Worker, 1974-1983 (Box 698, Folder 6)
- United National Association of Post Office Craftsmen, Publication (Box 699, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of National Officers of the Convention, 1922-1937 (Box 699, Folder 2)
    Author: United National Association of Post Office Craftsmen
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 699, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Switchmen's Light, 1961-1962 (Box 699, Folder 3)
    Author: Switchmen's Union of North America
- Teachers' Union of the City of New York, Publication (Box 699, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Schools Victory, 1942; Publication (Box 699, Folder 4)
    Author: Teachers' Union of the City of New York
    Notes: March
- Telecommunications International Union, Publication (Box 699, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual Convention, 1978; Publication (Box 699, Folder 5)
    Author: Telecommunications International Union
    Notes: May
- United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 699, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1973-1999 (Box 699, Folder 6)
- United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 699, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Agreement between the Staten Island Rapid Transit Operating Authority and the United Transportation Union, 1982; Publication (Box 699, Folder 7)
- United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 699, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: United Transportation Union Field Manual, 1975; Publication (Box 699, Folder 8)
- United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 699, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The United Transportation Union Handbook of Transportation in America, 1971; Publication (Box 699, Folder 9)